你确定这会没问题吗 罗伯特
You sure this is going to be alright, Robert?
是的 你会呆在楼下的客房吧
Yeah, you’re gonna be staying in the downstairs guestroom anyway.
这家伙永远不会知道是你而不是我
The guy’ll never know it was you and not me.
只要你不把这个地方烧了 一切都会好的
As long as you don’t burn the place down, everything will be fine.
你真的要保释我啊 安德烈
You’re really bailing me out here, Andre.
我的意思是 这件事情很快会被跟踪调查
I mean, this thing got fast tracked,
唯一的方式就是这周末我们把它结束
and the only way we’re gonna pull it off it  to do it this weekend.
又是什么
What is it again?
这个真人秀讲的就是
It’s this bullshit reality show where
我们把一些人放到有一堆摄像头的屋子里
we put somebody in a house with a bunch of security cameras
并观察他们的每个举动
that follows their every move
我们好好吓吓他们
And we scare the fuck out of them.
我们到了
Here we are.
来吧伙计 我要走了
Come on man.  I gotta hit the road.
我必须在七点的时候到他那里
I gotta be in SB by seven.
好吧
Alright.
怎么了
What is it?
这个地方的某些东西让我感觉似曾相识
Something about this place is really familiar.
那是因为你以前来过这里
That’s cause you’ve been here before.
什么
What?
是啊 是的 我们几年前去了那次聚会
Yeah!  Yeah, we went to that party here a couple of years ago.
你遇见了那个女孩 记得么
You met that girl, remember?
是的 她叫什么名字
Yeah…what was her name?
我不知道她叫什么名字
I don’t know what her name was.
我记得你所有的战利品
Think I remember all your conquests?
什么 战利品
Really?  Conquests?
尽管我并不记得她的名字了
I can’t remember her name though.
好吧 听着 这就是你为什么在这 好吗
Well look, that’s why you’re here, okay?
你要在这休息一段时间
You’re gonna rest for a few days.
你知道冰箱已经装满了
You know the fridge is fully stocked.
你知道的 享受你的时间吧
You know, take some you time.
你的时光 没有派对
You time.  No parties.
多谢老兄
Thanks man.
好的 不客气
Yeah, no problem.
听着 我周日会回来接你
Look, I’ll be back to pick you up on Sunday,
如果有什么问题给我打个电话
and if anything goes wrong give me a call.
听明白了 对吧
Got your cell, right?
是的
Yeah.
好的 很好
Okay.  Good.
祝你好运兄弟
Good luck man.
多谢
Thanks.
记住 不要举行聚会
Remember, no parties.
哇 那是什么
Wha, what was that?
你们要开派对
Throw a party?
如果你这么说的话
If you say so.
隔墙有眼
哦 这个地方糟糕透了
Oh, this place is sick.
所以 我 啊 我要被遗弃在这间房子里了
So…I ah, I got dropped off at this house.
这是个很好的房子
It’s a nice house,
这是由我的罗伯特老兄提供的
by ah my buddy Robert.
他本应该是看家的人
He was supposed to housesit for someone,
他不能看家因为一些事在最后关头出现
and he couldn’t cause something came up last minute.
老实说
To be honest.
有点奇怪 待在你不认识的人的家里
It’s kind of weird, being in someone’s house
你不认识他们任何人
when you don’t know who they are.
我确定我会找到更多的关于这个家伙的事情的
I’m sure I’ll figure out more about the guy as I rummage around through his shit.
嗯
Um.
只是最近在一次事故中
Was just recently in an accident,
医生说 我做一些视频日记
and the doctor said that doing video diaries, of myself,
可能会啊 虽然我不确定
would ah possibly, not for sure,
但可能帮助我记住东西
but possibly help me remember things.
所以啊 什么鬼啊
So ah…figured what the heck?
不妨尝试一下 如果它有效的话 酷
Ah, might as well give it a shot and if it works, cool.
如果没用 也没关系
If not?  It’s fine.
嗯 我要去给奶奶做一个生日视频
Um…Gonna go ahead and make Baba a little birthday video,
毕竟这个周日我要错过她的生日了
since I’m missing her birthday this weekend.
现在的话这里什么都没有
So here’s goes nothing.
奶奶好 大家好
Hey grandma and everyone.
我只是想说 我很抱歉
I just wanted to say I’m so sorry
我不能去参加你的庆祝活动
that I couldn’t make it out to your celebration.
啊 不幸的是 你知道我是多么容易发生事故
Ah, unfortunately you know how accident prone I am.
我很好 别担心 我会变得很好的
I’m okay, don’t worry I’ll be fine,
但是啊 因为我去不现场
but ah, since I couldn’t make it,
所以我想为你的第八十个生日做个庆祝视频
I thought I would make you a video for your eightieth birthday.
你是一个非常特别的女人
You’re a very special woman,
你看着一点也不像60多岁了
and you don’t look a day over sixty.
说的也是
That being said,
啊 为什么我不给你看看我的新地方的旅行
ah why don’t I give you a little tour of my new place.
这里是我的餐厅
This over here is my dining area.
好吧 让我们去看看这里的厨房吧
Alright, let’s go ahead and take a look at this kitchen here.
等一下 罗伯特说冰箱里备满了充足的食物
Wait, Robert did say the fridge was fully stocked.
我想看看他是不是在说谎
I want to see if he was lying or not.
而且啊 是的
And ah… yeah.
我看起来真的很不喜欢那些东西
That looks pretty shitty to me.
裸体的妹子 这也是加分项 不要介意
Naked girls.  That’s always a plus too.  Don’t mind it.
那是什么
What the hell is that?
哦 我的上帝
Oh my God.
我知道你是什么
I know what you are.
蓝色的梦 湿婆的臭鼬 紫色的噩
Blue Dream.  Shiva Skunk.  Purple OG.
姐妹 火噩 真都是什么乱七八糟的
Twisted Sister. Fire OG.  Happy four twenty.
我要把这个剪掉
I’ll have to edit this out.
我想举杯为你庆祝一下
I’d like to make a toast…to ah…
嗯 一个多么有趣的周末
well, what going to be one hell of an interesting weekend.
为了防止遗忘 我要一直抽着大麻
Gotta enough pot here to smoke myself into fucking oblivion…and
我还要有足够的酒让自己忙起来
ah, there’s plenty of booze to keep myself busy as well.
为自己干杯
Cheers to me.
真奇怪
Fuckin’ weird.
嘭
BOO!
这边 我们有娱乐室
Over here, we’ve got the entertainment room.
外面就像一个森林一样
It’s like a jungle outside.
好吧 我的烟 我的酒 而唯一我会缺的东西
Alright, I got the bud, I got the booze, and the only thing I’m missing…
就是电视
Is the Tv.
现在这将是一个漫长的周末
Now it’s gonna be a long weekend…and
啊 如果我有点孤独 我有我的
ah, if I get a bit lonely, I’ve got my…
可爱的女士们会让我忙不过来的
…lovely laides to keep me busy.
可能这边是客人区
It’s probably the guest area down there.
庆祝活动呢
And the festivities?
我准备好了
I am prepared.
我想知道后面是什么
I wonder what’s behind…
里面有什么
What’s in here?
储藏间
Storage.
一只小猫
Pussy.
哦 见鬼
Aw, shit.
主卧室 很好
The master bedroom.  Nice.
对不起 兄弟 但我肯定要睡在这里
Sorry buddy, but I’m definitely gonna have to crash here.
你是怎么做到的
How ya doing?
他甚至有好几个烟斗
He’s even got multi-jets.
这里有什么
What we got down here?
什么也没有
Nothing.
让我们去把这个拿出来
Let’s go ahead and take this out.
好啦
Okay.
这里也不是太简陋 我觉得能住在这
Not too shabby.  I can work with this.
这不是为你们而准备的 抱歉哦
That was not intended for you guys.  Sorry about that.
哇 这个地方比我想象的要大多了
Wow, this place is a lot bigger than I thought.
让我们看看这是哪里
Let’s see where this goes.
只是风 伙计们
Just the wind, folks.
好吧 我要走了 带你们回到里面
Alright, I’m gonna  go ahead and take you guys back inside.
几天前 一个年轻失踪的女孩的尸体
Now several days ago, the body of a young missing girl
在峡谷里的一辆汽车的行李箱里被发现了
was found in the trunk of a car, in the canyon.l
然而 却没有发现有司机活动的迹象
However there was no sign of the driver.
现在验尸报告显示 女孩的身体被残忍的刺伤
Now a coroner’s report indicates that the girl’s body was brutally stabbed…
并且她被折磨了好几天
And tortured over several days.
报告还表明 侦探并没有说Schow's的失踪
The report also indicates that the detectives are not saying whether Schow’s disappearance,
是否和那个被发现的可怕的失踪女孩有关系
and the grisly discovery of the missing girl are related.
但他们正在调查这两个女人的关系
But they are investigating connections to the two women.
如果你有任何相关情报信息 请打电话给警察
If you have any information, you are urged to call police.
现在播报其他新闻中 死刑犯正被运送到
Now in other news, inmates on death row are being transported to…
疯了吧
Crazy.
瑞秋宝贝 发生什么事了
Rachel.  What’s going on babe?
啊 这感觉很好
Ah, that felt good.
我今晚有约会 今晚 今晚
I gotta date tonight, tonight, tonight…
是的 我今晚有个约会 她的名字是
Yeah I gotta date tonight, and her name is…
她是瑞秋 不是蒂凡尼 不是安伯 是瑞秋
Rachel.  Not Tiffany.  Not Amber.  It’s Rachel.
瑞秋 瑞秋 瑞秋
Rachel.  Rachel.  Rachel.
我想出去兜风
Wanna go for a ride, ah…
但我没有车 我在说什么
oh wait I don’t have a car, what the fuck am I talking about?
是的 是有点可悲 我得买一辆
Yup.  Kinda pathetic.  I’ll have to get one.
这房子有一些奇怪的噪音
This house has got some weird noises.
你饿了吗
Are you hungry?
我确实饿了
I’m actually starving.
好吧
Good.
你给我带来好吃的东西了吗
You bring me something tasty?
我有一些鸡肉
I got some chicken,
但最重要的是我这里有一些真的很好的酒
but most importantly I got some really good wine.
啊 你真的是太好了
Awww, you’re so sweet.
你感觉如何
So how you feeling?
你知道 有点疼 还有点僵硬
You know, I’m a little sore, still stiff,
但是 大部分开始愈合
but ah…for the most part I’m starting to heal.
那么 究竟发生了什么
So… what actually happened?
好吧 当时在雨下
Well it was raining, and
啊 他们说我遭遇了车祸
ah,they said I was in a car accident,
我不幸被诊为脑震荡
and I got a concussion.
对我影响很大 我不记得太多了
That’s pretty much it.  I can’t remember much else.
你会记得吗 你还能不能回想起来
Are you ever going to be able to remember?
是的 医生说 希望有东西会唤起我的记忆
Yeah, the doctor said that hopefully something will jog my memory,
并在未来几天或几个月
and with in the next few days or months,
它会慢慢开始慢慢恢复的
it will slowly start coming back.
嗯 你不记得上次我们出去的时候发生了什么事吗
Hmm, so….you don’t remember what happened the last time we hung out?
没有 我应该记得吗
No.  Should I?
或许是
Maybe.
这个地方是如此的令人毛骨悚然的
This place is sooo creepy.
我不知道你怎么呆在这里 它没有吓坏你吗
I don’t know how you stay here.  Doesn’t it freak you out?
这是有一些令人毛骨悚然
It is kind of creepy.
所以啊 发生什么事了吗
So ahhhh, what happened?
嗯 我 啊 环顾四周
Well, I was ah, looking around, and
啊 我碰巧打开了一个橱柜门
ah, I happened to open up a cabinet door,
这些东西就掉到了地上
and this came crashing to the ground
所以你还是笨拙如初吗
So you’re still as clumsey as ever?
我想举杯庆祝一下
I’d like to make a toast.
好的 为了什么而庆祝
Okay.  To what?
敬你和我 永远记得这个奇妙的夜晚
Too you and I, and remembering this amazing evening.
嗯 我会的
Hmm.  I’ll make sure of that.
确实很好
That was good.
食物很美味 我吃饱了
Was delicious.  I’m stuffed.
这是什么
What’s this?
什么也不是啊
Ah nothing.
我啊 没法参加我奶奶的生日
I ahh, couldn’t make it to my grandma’s birthday,
所以我给她做了一个生日视频
so I like made her a birthday video.
不是吧你
No you didn’t?
是的没错 我那样做了
Yeah I did.
你真可爱
You’re cute.
你确定你不是为了其他事情而做的吗
You sure you didn’t put it out for something else?
不是
No.
啊 要不要一起吃晚饭
A little ahh…après dinner?
不 但我 我不要 但是我也我不反对
No but I’m, I’m not, I’m not opposed to it.
我能看看嘛
Can I watch it?
它真的 它就是 就是个
It’s really…it’s, it’s just a…
哦 来吧
Oh come on.
只是有点尴尬
It’s just embarrassing.
你真可爱
You’re so cute.
奶奶好 大家好
Hey grandma and everyone.
我只是想说 我很抱歉
I’m so sorry that
我不能去参加你的庆祝活动
I couldn’t make it out to your celebration.
啊 不幸的是 你知道我是多么容易变卦
Ah, unfortunately you know how accident prone I am.
我很好 别担心我会好的
I’m okay, don’t worry I’ll be fine,
但是啊 因为我去不了
but ah, since I couldn’t make it,
我想为你的第八十个生日做个视频
I thought I would make you a video for your eightieth birthday.
你是一个非常特别的女人 你看着还不到六十岁
You’re a very special woman, and you don’t look a day over sixty.
这只有我们吗
Are we alone?
是的
Yeah.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
是的
Yes.
看
Look.
你是一个非常特别的女人
You’re a very special woman,
你看着一点也不像60多岁了 嗯
and you don’t look a day over sixty.  Um.
好吧 这真的有点奇怪
Okay, this is really weird.
走去看看
Let’s go check it out.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
是的 挨着我不要走远
Yeah.  Just stay close.
好的
Okay.
别担心
Don’t worry.
好的
Okay.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
好啦
Yeah.
等一下
Wait. No.
别担心 没关系的
Don’t worry about it.  It’s fine.
好的 好的
Okay, okay.
好吧 她绝对没在动
Okay, she is definitely not moving.
不 绝对不是
Nope.  Definitely not.
我的直觉告诉我 罗伯特想要跟我搞事情
Something tells me Robert’s messing with me.
你这么觉得
You think?
我觉得我们喝的太多了
I think we had too much to drink.
我觉得我们应该再喝点
I think we should have a little more.
我要喝了这一杯
I’m gonna cover this up.
你在等什么人吗
Are you expecting someone?
没有 拿着这个
No.  Hold this.
嗨 啊
Hi, ah…
看 我 我真的很抱歉打扰你
Look, I’m, I’m really sorry to bother you.
我的伙计 我的生活在街对面的房子里
My name’s Guy,  and I live, ahh, four houses up the street.
什么
Yeah?
看
Look.
警察没有给你打电话 对吗
You didn’t just get a call from the police, did you?
呃 什么
Uhhh, excuse me?
听着 我知道这听起来很奇怪
Look, I know this sounds strange
但我只是接到警方电话说有一群逃犯
but I just got a call from the police sayingthere was a group of escaped
在峡谷某个地方藏着你知道吗
convicts loose somewhere in the canyon, ya know?
我不知道这是一种把戏还是
I don’t know if this is some kind of game or,
你没有听说过这个 你听过吗
you haven’t heard anything about this, have you?
不 我没有
No I didn’t.
你确定这不是一个恶作剧
Are you sure it’s not maybe a prank?
我不 我不知道 它 听起来不像它
I don’t, I don’t know.  It..it didn’t sound like it.
他们让我确保我所有的窗户和门都被锁上了
They asked me to make sure that all my windows and doors were locked,
并要仔细检查一切 这些是你的吗
and to double check everything.  Are yours?
嗯 我不知道 我觉得是这样
Um, I don’t know.  I. I think so.
你觉得吗 你不确定吗
You think so?  You’re not sure?
你现在就得去检查一下
You need to go right now and check it.
我们还好吗
Are we okay?
嗨 我是盖伊 我是你们的邻居
Hi, I’m Guy, I’m the neighbor,
我刚接到了一个警察的电话
and I just got a police bulliten saying
说这附近有一群逃犯逃过来了
there’s a group of escaped convicts loose in the neighborhood.
现在没有确定的说法
Now there’s no guarrante that
他们可能会在这里造反 但以防万一
they might make it up here, but just in case.
所以这一切是什么时候发生的
So when did this all happen?
我刚刚才接到了电话
I just got the phone call.
嗯 你的窗户看起来是安全的 门也锁着
Well your windows up here seem to be secure.  Doors locked.
我的意思是 我不知道该说什么
I mean, I don’t know what to say.
窗户
Window.
这真是一个非常好的地方
This is a really nice place you got here.
嗯
Um.
如果你想继续的话
If you want to keep it this way,
我建议你一定要确保所有的窗户和门都锁上了
I suggest you make sure all your windows and doors are locked.
你说你住的房子离这里很近啊
And you said you lived just a couple house…
我刚搬进有四个门的西班牙别墅
I just moved into the Spanish villa four doors up.
啊 这是在地下室吗
Ahh, is this the downstairs?
是的 我不是有意冒犯您 我很感激你能来这里
Yeah.  I..I don’t mean to be rude, I appreciate you coming here.
嗯 你介意和她呆在一起吗
Um, would you mind staying here with her?
不 不介意
No, not at all.
你同意吗
You okay with that?
嗯
Yeah.
我要 啊 去检查其他的一切
I’ll ah, go check out everything else.
当然啦
Of course.
谢谢你
Thank you.
别客气啦
My pleasure.
是你给警察打的电话吗
Have you called the police?
噢 他们给我打的
Oh, they called me.
噢 确保检查好每扇门和窗都锁好
Oh and make sure you check every door and window.
当然啦
Sure thing.
一个都别漏掉
Don’t miss one.
马上就回来了 瑞秋
Be right back, Rach.
是的 真是个美好的夜晚对吧
Yeah.  Crazy night, right?
是的
Yeah.
这真是个好地方
This really is a nice place.
这简直太疯狂了
This is insane.
是的 没有什么比警察
Yeah.  Nothing like a police
毁了一个美好的约会更疯狂的了
emergency to ruin somebody’s night.
知道我怎么想的吗
Know what I mean?
所以 你们两个在一块多长时间了
So, how long have you two been seeing each other?
噢 就不到一会
Oh, just a little while.
你们俩在一起很搭
Make a cute couple.
你不觉得这有些奇怪吗
You don’t find these a little creepy?
需要我给你拿点东西喝吗
Can I get you anything?
哦 不 不 不 不用了 谢谢你
Oh, no, no, no, I’m okay, thank you.
我就在这待一会
I’ll be going in just a minute.
你们两个在一起睡了多久了
So, how long have you two been fucking?
你说什么 这不关你的事
Excuse me?  That’s none of your business.
对不起 我就随便一问
Sorry.  Just asking.
所以 啊 当你们做爱的时候
So ahh, when you guys fuck,
他亲你的脸 你的屁股 或你的胸部吗
does he come on your face, or ass or your tits?
哇哦
Wow.
我 你该走了 额 我自己没问题的
I…it’s, it’s time for you to go now.Uhh, I’m fine.
啊 安德烈
A..ah..Andre.
哦 我并不担心你叫他
Oh, I wouldn’t worry about that.
安德烈听不见的 你在房间的另一端
Andre can’t hear you.  He’s all the way at the back of the house.
很不幸声音传不了那么远
Unfortunately the sound doesn’t travel… that far.
我要带上我的手套出去一下
I’ll just get my gloves on,and I’ll be out in a minute.
我不想把我的指纹留在任何东西上 我现在要留吗
Wouldn’t want to get my fingerprints on anything, now would I?
我 我真的很不舒服 你必须要走了
I…I’m really uncomfortable.  You have to go now.
哦 我会走的
Oh, I’ll leave.
好 太好了
Okay, great.
你走了我就走
Just as soon as you leave.
好了 我把所有东西检查过了
Alright…I checked everything.
看到了吧 这不是很难完成的一件事 对吗
See…now that wasn’t so hard.  Was it?
不是太糟糕 尽管博若莱今年的状态比以前要好的很多
Not bad.  Although the Beaujolais is much better at this time of year.
瑞秋怎么了
What happened to Rachel?
她刚刚走了
She just left.
是的 她拿着她的东西走了
Yup, She took her shit.  She’s gone.
她走了她有说为什么吗
She left?  Did she say why?
没有 就带着她的东西 摔了东西 走出了那扇门
No.  Just took her shit and walked out the door.
说不通啊 她来这是为了跟我一起吃饭啊
Doesn’t make any sense.  She came her to have dinner with me.
为什么她就这么走了啊
Why would she just pick up and go?
你问着我了 你是她的约会对象
You got me.  You’re the date.
我来就是为了跟你谈谈罪犯的事
I just came by to tell you…about the criminals.
好吧 你跟她说什么了吗
Well, did you say anything to her?
哦 得了吧安德烈 别开始怪我啊
Oh, come on Andre.  Don’t start blaming this one me.
我来这是帮你忙的啊
I came here to help you out.
来帮我忙的 我不太明白
Help me out, I mean I don’t understand…this
直到你出现之前整晚都过得很好
whole night was going perfect until you showed up.
听着 你不能只会推卸责任老兄
Look…You can’t just keep passing the buck man.
你自己的问题别怪我
Don’t blame me for your short comings.
你可是五英尺半的大汉 你怎么能这样呢 上帝啊
Five and a half inches.  Jesus Christ.
你说什么
Excuse me?
五英尺半 她这样说的
Five and half inches.  That’s what she said.
瑞秋永远不会说出那样的话的
Rachel would never say anything like that.
好吧 你应该给她打电话问问
Well maybe you should call her up and ask her.
天哪 老兄
Jesus, man.
你觉得你是谁啊
Who a…who do you think you are?
其实就是一个邻居在找另一个人
Just a neighborly friend looking out for…another guy.
你在找我吗 你在找我
You’re looking our for me?  You are looking out for me?
我想你可以走了
I’d like you to leave.
你要我走么
You want me to go?
但是你准备了酒和晚餐 我能帮你解决掉它吗
But, you’ve got wine and dinner, I could help you finish?
我说了什么吗
Did I say something?
我说 你赶快出去
I said…get…the fuck…out.
哇 好吧 不用告诉我这么多遍了
Whoa…okay.  Don’t have to tell me three times.
听着 安德烈 跟你在一起绝对是件快乐的事
Look, it’s been an absolute pleasurej Andre.
我现在马上就走
I’ll just be getting out of your hair now.
你知道 我真的很喜欢你在这里做的事情
You know, I really like what you’ve done with the place.
哎 瑞秋走了 真是太糟糕了
It’s too bad Rachel left.
我再说一遍 如果你需要我的帮助的话
And again, if you need anything
我就在马路那边 随时来找我 回见 哈
I’ll just be right up the road. See you around, huh?
你都在说些什么
What the fuck was that?
你一定是在跟我开玩笑
You gotta be kidding me.
没有人管吗
Where’s that charger?
哦 该死
Oh, fuck.
管理员呢 没有人管管吗
Where’s the charger?  Where is the charger?
屋里一定有电话
There’s gotta be a house phone somewhere.
我不信我竟然找不到充电器
I can’t believe I can’t find a fucking charger.
这个家伙屋里的电话呢
Where’s this guy’s house phone?
这是什么
What the fuck was that?
让我看看这个还能用不能了
Let’s see if this works.
来吧
Come on.
哦 该死
Ohhh, fuck
嘿 我是瑞秋
Hey it’s Rach.
你知道什么时候该做什么
You know what to do, and when to do it.
瑞秋 我是安德烈
Rachel, it’s Andre.
听着 我根本不知道
Look I don’t know
那个家伙跟你说了什么 或者对你做了什么
what the Hell that fucking creep said to you, or did to you,
但我很担心你 我的手机也坏了
but I’m worried about you, and my phone is fucking dead
我找不到我的充电器了
and I can’t find my charger.
所以 你收到这条消息就尽快给我打个电话
So as soon as you get this message,give me a call back on this number.
请你一定要给我打回来
Please call me back.
我希望你没事
I hope you’re alright.
真是该死
Fucking bastard.
嘿 怎么了伙计
Hey, what’s up man?
你惹到我了 你这个混蛋
You got me.  You son of a bitch.
你在说什么
What’re you talking about?
你知道我在说什么
You know exactly what I’m talking about.
我知道你在耍我 这也是你让我在这的原因
I know you wanted to put me in the show, and that’s why you had me here.
这很有意思 但是够了 停止这一切吧
It’s…it’s funny but enoughs, enough.  Let’s just call it quit’s huh?
是的 你说对了 我没耍你
Yeah right.  You’re not on the show man.
啊 你再说一遍这个房子是谁的
Wh, who, who’s house did you say this was again?
啊 我一个朋友的 我告诉过你了
Ah, a good friend of mine.  I told you that.
是的 是的 但我的意思是 你了解他多少
Yeah, yeah, but I mean..how well do you know him?
为什么他有瑞秋的照片
Why does he have photos of Rachel?
等等 你在哪
Wait.  Where are you?
我 我在办公室 我需要给瑞秋打个电话
I…I’m in the office, I needed the phone because Rachel…this,
因为有个奇怪的家伙过来了
this weirdo came over.
他把她吓跑了 我想确定一下瑞秋是否有事
He scared her away, and I wanted to make sure she’s alright,
但我的手机坏了 我来这找个电话用
but my phone’s dead so I came to find a phone.
听着安德烈 别紧张
Look Andre, just calm down.
你让我怎么不紧张
Calm the fuck down?
我应该怎么冷静下来 这个混蛋
How am I supposed to calm down?  This is fucking weird.
听我说 安德烈 我没跟你在一块
Andre listen to me.  I’m not fucking with you.
你没被耍 我也不知道发生了什么
You’re not on the show and I don’t know what’s going on over there,
但在你做出什么混蛋事之前你得先冷静下来
but you gotta calm down before you do something dumb.
你听到我说什么了么
Do you hear me?
你的医生说你那是因为脑震荡和记忆力减退
Didn’t your doctor you that because of the concussion and
所以你有点偏执是正常的
the memory loss that a little bit of paranoia is normal?
是的 我想是的
Yeah I guess.
对吗
Right?
是的
Yeah.
安德烈 你不能离开
Andre, you cannot leave.
你这样做的话 我们就都完蛋了
You do that and we are both fucked,
因为他会发现我不在那里
cause he’s gonna find out I wasn’t there.
相信我 瑞秋没事
Trust me, Rachel is fine.
我的意思是我猜她也没事 但
I mean I guess so but…
你应该看看这些照片
You gotta see these photos.
你要怎么办
What’re you gonna do?
难道你要沿着山走 找她吗
Walk down the hill and look for her?
瑞秋没事
Rachel is fine.
没关系 实际上 她不应该出现在那里的
Nevermind the fact that she shouldn’t have been there at all.
所以你只是想找个伴
So you do what you gotta do to grow a pair.
拜托了兄弟 从那个房间走出来 放松点
Just please man, get out of that room, and go relax.
好吧 听起来是个好主意
Alright, that sounds like a good idea.
听着 我不是想让你惹麻烦
Look, I’m not trying to get you in trouble.
我知道 只是
I know man, just…
我要给自己弄杯喝的 都会好起来的
I’m gonna go make myself a nice drink and…everything will be fine.
你可以做到的
You can do this man.
好了 我知道了
Alright.  See ya.
真是超强
That’s fucking strong.
哈
Ahh
哈喽 里面有人吗
Hello?  Is anybody in there?
我们进去看吧
Let’s go ahead, and take a look in here.
不管你在哪 出来吧 出来
Come out, come out where ever you are.
不 不 你不想出来嘛
Nope, nope.  You don’t want to come?
那是什么
What was that?
那是伊丽莎白·赛维
That’s Elisabeth Sellwin,
在1692年被众人当成巫婆三世烧死
burned as a witch March third, sixteen ninety two.
是的 当我走进这个城镇的时候我注意到了那块匾
Yes I know I saw the plaque as I was walking into town.
到底发生了什么 到底发生了什么
What the fuck is going on?  What the fuck is going on?
哈哈哈 真搞笑
Ha, ha, ha, real fucking funny.
该死 我要出去
Fuck this shit.  I’m getting the fuck outta here.
我要干嘛
What am I gonna fucking do?
我到底要干嘛
What the fuck am I gonna do?
我告诉你你要干什么 你要变得男人起来
I’ll tell you what you’re gonna do.  You’re gonna man the fuck up!
把它合在一起
Get it together.
胡扯
Shit.
到底怎么了
What the fuck?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
摸我
Touch me.
所以你打算对我做什么
So what are you gonna do to me?
宝贝
Baby?
那是个玩具吗
Is that a toy?
你为什么不说话
Why aren’t you talking?
宝贝
Babe?
过来
Come here.
那是什么
What is that?
你在哪
Where are you?
怎么了
What the fuck?
我什么都看不到了
I can’t fucking see anything.
我要试着找个断路器或者其他什么东西
I’m gonna try and go find the circuit breaker or something.
这黑得像个地狱
It’s fucking dark as hell.
我不知道该干什么了
I don’t know what the fuck to do.
我觉得有人想害我
I think someone is fucking with me right now.
哦混蛋
Oh shit.
怎么回事
What the fuck?
哦 天哪
Oh shit.
哦天哪 哦 混蛋 混账
Oh shit.  Oh fuck, oh fuck, oh fuck.
安德烈
Andre?
瑞秋 是你吗
Rachel?  Is that you?
到底怎么了
What the fuck!?
哦 上帝啊
Oh my God.
那到底是什么啊 到底是什么
What the fuck was that?  What the fuck was that?
哦 上帝 是什么
Oh my God.  What the fuck?
到底怎么了 发什么神经
What the fuck.  Get the fuck.
该死的 混账
Fucking shit.  Fuck.
滚得远点 滚得远点
Get the fuck off me.  Get the fuck off of me.
怎么了
What the fuck?
下来
Get down!
快点下来到地上
Get down on the ground!
你在干嘛 你抓错人了
What’re you doing?  You got the wrong person.
他在房子里
He’s in the house!
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
嘿 你们这些家伙在干吗
Hey, what are you guys doing?
他在屋里 啊嗷 混蛋东西
He’s in the house!  Owww!  Fuck!
听我说 他在房子里
He’s in the house.  Just listen.
放松 放松
Relax.  Relax.
我告诉你 你们抓错人了 他在屋里
I’m telling you, you’ve got the wrong guy.  He’s in the fucking house!
放轻松
Relax!
你
You.
你搞什么鬼 你
What the fuck, you…
啊 这太紧了
Ahhh, it’s fucking tight.
闭嘴
Stop.
我能证明 你就放一下视频
I can prove it.  Just play the fucking video.
好吧 我有视频证据
Alright, there’s a video on there.
它会向你证明我是清白的
It’ll show you.
求你了 放一下吧
Just play the video please.
不不
No.  No.
不
No
不可能 不
No way.  No.
祝你好运兄弟
Good luck, man.
谢谢你 我真是太谢谢你了
Thank you.  I appreciate it.
你一定会的 回见
You bet.  See ya.
不
No!
他们说我是因为车祸才失去记忆的
They said that I was in a car accident, and I got a concussion,
不
No!
我真的很喜欢你在那个地方做的一切
I really like what you’ve done with the place.
希望什么东西能唤醒我的记忆
Hopefully something will jog my memory.
不要啊
Noooooooo!
哦 上帝
Oh my God!
不 不要啊 不这不是真的
No.  Noooo.  No.  This isn’t real.
很多 这不可能是真的
Fuck!  This can’t be real.
把它关了 快把它关了吧 求你了
Turn it off.  Just turn it off.  Please.
真是个噩梦
It’s a bad dream.
我没想那么做
I didn’t want to do it to her.
他让我对她这样的
He made me do this to her.
我没想那么做
I didn’t want to do it.
请别再逼我了 我做不到
Please stop fucking with me.  I can’t take it.
看屏幕 你个混蛋
Look at the screen, you pussy.
你们这些家伙肯定都出去了
You boys sure went all out.
我的意思是 这所有的一切都是针对我么
I mean…all this?  For me?
我不得不承认 我有点受宠若惊
I gotta admit.  I’m kind of flattered.
这一切都是扯淡 这些人都在周围藏着吗
All this bullshit.  Hiding all around the place?
就等着抓我
Chasing me?
你们想过你们这样会吓到我的
And you actually thought for a moment that you had me scared.
我会被吓到吗
Me scared?
你就是那个混蛋 安德烈
Yeah maybe that bitch, Andre.
你看到我要做什么了吗
You see what I have to put up with?
这该死的臭女人
This fucking pussy.
日复一日 日复一日
Day in, and day out.
我甚至都不能再看他一眼
I can’t even fucking look at him anymore.
看他 可怜的那样
Look at him.  Pathetic.
她每一秒都是那么的享受
She fucking enjoyed every second of it.
每一秒都是
Every second of it.
真是个傻子
Fucking idiot.
如果他肯听话的话
If he’d only just listened.
控制不了任何事
Can’t control anything.
亚当控制着一切
Adam controls everything.